<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Secret of Unconditional Happiness]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Secret of Unconditional Happiness]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/food-pics/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 21:51:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/food-pics/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 21:51:41 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unconditional Happiness Emersion Experience]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Unconditional Happiness Emersion Experience</strong></h1>,<h2>What’s It All About?</h2>,<p><strong>Have you ever thought …</strong></p>,<p><strong>“I will be happy … </strong></p>,<ul><li>If only this situation were different … </li></ul>,<ul><li>If only my husband/wife/partner would act differently … </li></ul>,<ul><li>If only my children were better behaved …</li></ul>,<ul><li>When I get that promotion …</li></ul>,<ul><li>When I can afford to retire to the south of Spain …</li></ul>,<ul><li>When I lose weight …</li></ul>,<ul><li>When I have more confidence …</li></ul>,<ul><li>When I’m better qualified</li></ul>,<ul><li>If I could achieve enlightenment …</li></ul>,<ul><li>If I were a better parent / teacher / coach / dancer …</li></ul>,<ul><li>If more people liked me</li></ul>,<ul><li>When I win the lottery!</li></ul>,<p>Have you noticed - these are all versions of what we might call the “I’ll be happy when…” trap that we all fall into from time to time - or all the time.</p>,<p>But what if we’ve innocently got it the wrong way round?&nbsp; </p>,<p>What if our happiness, our wellbeing, our peace of mind doesn’t depend on what we currently think it does - but is in fact our default state of being?</p>,<p>What would be the implications of that?</p>,<p>What would become available to you - what would you experience - if you knew, in your bones that was true?</p>,<p><strong>Imagine yourself... </strong></p>,<p>FREE - of any need for things to be different, in order for you to BE HAPPY NOW</p>,<p>FREE - to LOVE YOUR LIFE - unconditionally</p>,<p>FREE - to DO THINGS YOU LOVE TO DO - without imagining your happiness or your wellbeing depend on any particular outcome.</p>,<p>Join Anne and Vivienne …
for a relaxed and fun five-day deep immersion experience - in the beautiful and relaxed setting of the Camping Beau Rivage, in the ancient walled town of Navarrenx at the foot of the French Pyrenees. </p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e56fe378-31cd-422d-853c-38553ab7ec61.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4f9fc90f-52fb-4e48-bacb-d43b05f5e6ba.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bc7d1d71-cd93-446a-836e-6743db3c2336.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e375755a-e698-45a6-864a-530d5fab5cfb.jpg">,<p>Together we will explore - and experience deeply - the unconditional nature of happiness, of wellbeing, of resilience and of peace of mind.&nbsp; </p>,<p>Can we guarantee you’ll see something new about your own “I’ll be happy when…”? </p>,<p>No (because we’re not in charge of your insights or realisations) but we guarantee we’ll point you in the most helpful direction to see something that could literally set you free.</p>,<p>P.S. There is absolutely NOTHING you can throw at us that is an exception to this - our natural way of being and experiencing happiness.&nbsp; </p>,<p>From childlessness - to relationship woes, from anxieties about your body, your health, your finances and the future - to traumatic past experience - we will help you to see - and to deeply experience - that your happiness now and in the future is completely independent of any of those things.</p>,<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/food-pics/unconditional-happiness-emersion-experience/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">adb45cdb-24af-4f20-bf77-c56f14003873</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:12:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>